Sharjeel Ahmad Software Engineer

■ sharjeelahnmed5@gmail.com

• Lahore, Pakistan

1999/12/16

+923014530509

■ Pakistani

ېت Male

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sharjeel-ahmad-

.

772ab328b

O +923014530509

github.com/sharjeel1122-lab

Summary

I am a Flutter Developer and choose to design lively mobile application. I have experience in flutter, custom dart development and android programming where I code and create mobile apps that are compatible on different platforms. I am well-versed in GetX for managing the state and making sure the application can run smoothly and can handle the scales when needed. I have experience in other widgets such as custom animations and handling Future and Stream to perform asynchronous operations as well as normal, complex and special widgets in the Flutter package to create a simple, effective and functional user interface.

Professional Experience

2024/04 – present Flutter Developer
Lahore, Pakistan At Innovation High Tech

2023/08 - 2024/03 Flutter Developer Internship

Lahore, Pakistan At Incendio Solutions

Education

2019/05 - 2024/05 Bachelor of Science in Software Engineering

Lahore, Pakistan Superior University

Projects

Mobile Application Development

Flutter Framework

Projects Completions:

- AI-Ponics Control Panel app
- AgriSight App
- Smart Ghar App
- Tekken 8 Framedata App

WordPress

Elementor

- Corsa Studios
- Pakistan Agro Show
- AquaDome Hub

Certificates

Wordpress & Freelancing & Digital Marketing Clinial Assistant

Virtual University Vocational Training Institute

SQL

CCTV, MS office and Graphic Designing

The Brains College Online Platform

Skills

Getx, Provider, MVVM, Firebase, Android HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, WordPress and Corel draw,